ANZU NAKAYAMA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Address: Vancouver, B.C. Phone: 236-878-7420

E-mail: anzunakayama@gmail.com

GitHub: anznk

LinkedIn: <u>anzu-nakayama-0660641b1</u>

website: <u>anzunakayama.dev</u>

PERSONAL PROFILE

Front-end developer with over 5 years of experience in software development and front-end web development. Specializes in React.js and JavaScript. These skills in addition to my passion for learning and my dedication to getting the job done will serve you well.

EXPERIENCE

Front-end developer

NTT docomo Inc., Tokyo | 2017 - 2019

- Developed, maintained and tested the company's website for inbound tourists with JavaScript, JQuery, HTML5, CSS3
- · Made a requirement definition document
- Developed the website until the deadline
- Increased new registration rate by 30%
- Analyzed the company's website for marketing, SEO purposes

Software developer

NTT docomo Inc., Tokyo | 2014 - 2017

- Developed Supply Chain Management (SCM) system using C, Java, Oracle SQL
- Wrote SQL queries to retrieve data from the database using Oracle Database
- Did unit-testing, Integration testing, functional testing and detected bugs and their causes
- Prioritized Development Roadmap to complete projects on time
- Instructed new team members.

EDUCATION

Web and Mobile Application Development Co-op Diploma

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada Vancouver, B.C. | 2019 - 2020

• React.js, Node.js, Express.js, JavaScript, Java, Python

Bachelor of Arts

Hosei University Tokyo, Japan | 2010 - 2014

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- React.js, Node.js, Express.js, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Sass
- Oracle SQL, MySQL, MongoDB, Firebase
- Java, C, Python